# YULIIA SHCHERBYNA

# **Junior Front End Developer**

**+380500841379** 

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuliia-shcherbyna-

@ julia\_19932008@ukr.net

**♥** Kiev, Ukraine



# **SUMMARY**

I'm a motivated and enthusiastic Junior Frontend Developer, I possess a solid foundation in web development and well-versed in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and Node.js. While I may not have prior experience working specifically as a Frontend Developer, my diverse background spanning over a decade in various fields has instilled in me the ability to adapt quickly and excel in new environments and my first step in IT as an SEO manager is a proof.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### SEO manager

Dev.Up

🛱 12/2022 - Present

Remote

#### Waitress

**Princess Cruises** 

## Manager

Remax

**=** 09/2020 - 02/2021

Scottsdale, AZ

#### Actor

**=** 2019 - 2022

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor, TV-host **Kiev International University** 

**=** 2010 - 2014

# **TECH STACK**

HTMI **CSS React Native** 

**React Redux Angular NodeJS** 

Git MongoDB

# **LANGUAGES**

Ukrainian

Native

**English** 

B2



# TRAINING / COURSES

**Space Study** 

Front-End Developer

### **PASSIONS**

Reading

**Traveling** 

Yoga